janbrett.com 2002-10-14

# Privacy Statement

## Privacy Statement for [www.janbrett.com](http://www.janbrett.com/)  

     Jan Brett has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate a firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses information gathering and dissemination practices for this website: **www.janbrett.com**.

     This site contains links to other sites. **www.janbrett.com** is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.  No information gathered on **www.janbrett.com** is shared with any of these sites.

**Newsletter and n ote to Parent** **s**

     We offer a free online newsletter on our site in which we ask visitors for their email address and we run contests in which we ask visitors for their school addresses. The visitor's contact information is used to contact the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below.   No information gathered on **www.janbrett.com** is shared with any other person, group, or organization.

   Our site provides parents the following option for removing their children's information from our database to not receive future communications. 

     You can send email to [janbrett@janbrett.com](mailto:janbrett@janbrett.com).

## Children's Guidelines

  1. We do NOT request personally identifiable offline home contact information (home postal addresses).
  2. We do NOT distribute to third parties anyone's email address or any other information.
  3. We do NOT sell or offer for sale any products.  All materials on **www.janbrett.com** are available to everyone at no charge.
  4. We do NOT entice by the prospect of a special game, prize or other activity, a child to divulge more information than is needed to participate in the activity

## Public Forums

     This site has a  message board  available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in this area becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.  The message board is monitored on a daily basis.

## Choice/Opt-Out

    Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us .   This site gives users the following option for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications.

    You can send email to [janbrett@janbrett.com](mailto:janbrett@janbrett.com)

## Correct/Update

     This site gives users the following option for changing and modifying information previously provided.

    Email [janbrett@janbrett.com](mailto:janbrett@janbrett.com)

## Contacting the Web Site

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact   Jan Brett Post Office Box 366 Norwell, Ma. 02061   janbrett@janbrett.com

Home Page
